[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these actors did not participate in the 2004 movie Crash?", "correct_answer": "Heath Ledger", "incorrect_answers": ["Tony Danza", "Jennifer Esposito", "Brendan Frazer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why are Charles Dickens books so wordy?", "correct_answer": "He got paid by the word", "incorrect_answers": ["He knew he had a short life and wanted to get everything on paper", "That was the style of the day", "He didnt want anyone to say Please Sir! More gruel!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The origin of the word denim is related to the name of which southern French city?", "correct_answer": "Nimes", "incorrect_answers": ["Genoa", "Nantes", "Montpellier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The portrayal of which of these characters brought Tom Hanks an Academy Award for Best Actor?", "correct_answer": "Andrew Beckett", "incorrect_answers": ["James A. Lovell", "Chuck Noland", "Captain John H. Miller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The meninges, a system of membranes that envelop the central nervous system, consist of three layers. Which of the following is not  a name of a layer?", "correct_answer": "grey mater", "incorrect_answers": ["dura mater", "pia mater", "archanoid mater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chocolate is low in caffeine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the play the students preform in High School Musical 3?", "correct_answer": "Senior Year", "incorrect_answers": ["High School Musical", "Guys and Doll", "Twinkle Town"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ruled by Mercury, people born under this sign are really clever. It is typical for them to constantly try to separate what is useful from what is not.", "correct_answer": "Virgo", "incorrect_answers": ["Pisces", "Leo", "Sagittarius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Alfred in the 2005 movie Batman Begins?", "correct_answer": "Michael Caine", "incorrect_answers": ["Efrem Zimbalist Jr.", "Ian McKellen", "Bernard Hill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Slovenia?", "correct_answer": "Ljubljana", "incorrect_answers": ["Prague", "Bratislava", "Zagreb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What plant is poisonous for guinea pigs and should never be offered to them?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["All plants growing from a bulb", "Bracken", "Wild celery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What size are Carters bowling shoes in the movie Princess Protection Program?", "correct_answer": "7/8", "incorrect_answers": ["8/9", "6/7", "5/6"]}]